(upbeat music)
- And we are live.
- Yes.
- Welcome back on the Shibshid show.
- You had to miss us a whole week.
- Yeah.
- Michel?
- Yes.
- How's life, how was your day?
- Well, I think we hacked cloud Opus today, right?
- Right, I don't know what's going on with that shit.
Like, bro, like you said, you type hello world
and then you are at 50%.
- Yeah, and you don't have, you cannot make a typo.
- Because it will cost you an additional 10%.
- Yeah, like I spent my day like rewriting my skills,
like all of the repo, like cleaning up all of the skills,
stuff like that, done grading the CLI.
- Yes, that was the best one.
- Yeah, 1%.
So I watched like a couple of, yeah,
there was videos and stuff and explain
like why the fuck it's going.
And like some guys are able to compare result
and yeah, they have the numbers,
they're legit burning more tokens to less,
but to fall a shittier result.
- Yeah, get less results, pay more.
- Yeah, exactly.
I mean, it's a good business model.
- Yeah, well, not that good.
I think people are leaving.
- I think so, like, I keep my subscription
because I know they will fix it
and they will, like the next release
should be hopefully better.
But, and I think we will have a ping pong to do
like all the time we're between cloud and codex anyway,
like yeah, OpenAI, so.
- Yeah, but still, they release a new update.
You get automatically updated in your CLI.
So you have no choice.
Cloud code just goes to Opus 4.7
and there is no explanation, no documentation.
You just know, because all the people on X posting,
they have figured it out and they say it's worse.
And then after a day you get blocked
because you're out of tokens.
- Yeah, no, it's not like, yeah.
I use my weekly stuff on a day or two
and maybe it's about the skills and stuff,
but codex are loading the same,
like I have global skills for both, right?
And codex, I've got everything
with X I effort and it works perfectly.
- Yeah, but also now you're rolled back to 4.6, right?
- Yes, yes.
So for, I didn't even upgrade it
because yeah, like you said, like the.
- Oh yeah, you had the automatic upgrading disabled.
- Yeah, so there is that, but so, yeah.
So I don't grade it to the CLI, the stable one
and I never changed the model 4.7.
- So maybe for the viewers, if you go to the cloud folder
and you change the settings file,
- Yeah.
- Just disable automatic updates.
- Yeah, I will have the tweets.
Oh yeah, because we've been talking about that.
- Yeah, we can say we know how to downgrade
and how to disable it,
but I don't know if everybody knows what it is.
- Tech, path, pack, apply.
That's what, yeah, what's that we have done?
Downgraded to 2.1.96, blah, blah, blah.
Disable enable tool search
and auto update channels, auto update channels stable.
I think that's the most important one.
I think disable the tool search
because like there's one guy talking about it.
I suggest to use code stable.
It's the same as three,
but can be done at the terminal shell
and the current stable release is a 2.1.5.
And it was like 20 days ago, almost 15 days ago.
So basically a lifetime in AI, but.
- But normally you just always work on stable, right?
And you only update when you disable it.
- I had, I do like a brew upgrade every day.
- Ah, okay.
- So yeah.
- Yes, last version is the best one.
- Exactly, yeah, it's supposed to be.
But because of that,
I expected to only get the stable version.
And if I do upgrade, I stay on the stable path
because of that config, but it's cool.
- Yeah.
- And I didn't do that and it's fine.
- But how I understood it,
they just are trying to tweak cloud to be more.
- Yeah, more.
- Be better and then.
- So like Theo explained that where,
so also there is some hardware behind the hood,
like from Entropic.
For every request, you can get dispatched to another server
and a server can be on another hardware
and AI doesn't function, just works the same
if it's using a Nvidia server or like something else
or even GPU, whatever, whatever.
If it's a different hardware,
you will get two different outputs.
- Yes.
- And you get different routing to a different server,
every search tool, every,
so all the time you are talking to somewhere else.
- Yeah, well, that makes sense why it's more expensive.
- Yeah, talk about non-deterministic outputs, they're no shit.
- But we fixed it.
- Yeah, but just like. - For now.
- Yeah, yeah, just going back to the future of the past.
- But are you going to test every update?
Are you just waiting for people
to explain what they are doing?
- Yeah, I will wait for my subscription to reset first.
(laughing)
- Yeah.
- And yeah, we'll see, like, okay.
I think if it works, I will not upgrade shit
until like another model.
I think I'll avoid all of the fucking CLI update stuff
between two models, 'cause fuck it.
Like I don't want to spend days
on configuring like cloud dot settings.
- Yeah, that's ID rule one.
If it works, don't touch it.
- Yeah, except with AI, when they push something
and then it gives you 50% more token.
Oh, that's token, that's interesting.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, but anyway, there was a big update
while we were searching for a topic
for the live stream that happened, like it was live.
- Yeah, it's daily updates.
- Yes, yeah, we should do more than one a week,
but yeah, when we will have an audience.
So if you are here, please like and subscribe
because every view counts, so.
- Thank you, thank you.
- Yeah, thank you, thank you.
And I don't think there's anybody.
That's okay.
- One moment.
- Oh, sure.
Oh yeah, thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Tag.
Thank you, okay, nice.
So why we were basically 30 minutes ago,
no, one hour ago, one, nope, this one, yes.
- This one.
- So one hour ago, OpenAI with GPT images 2.0,
and it's great, it's fantastic.
- You already tried it?
- Yes, to make the thumbnail of this live stream.
- Cool.
- So, but we are going to try it even more together
because yeah, I want you to like have me prompt
some crazy stuff.
- Let's see how it works.
- Okay, I'm gonna zoom in.
Okay, wait, video path.
So a state of thought image model that can take
on complex visual tasks and produce precise immediately,
immediately usable visual with sharper editing,
rich layout and syncing level intelligence.
There is syncing into this image model.
So it's interesting because instead of like a loading
OpenAI logo into your image output,
you can reference OpenAI logo as,
and then it will go as a web search.
- Oh, that's cool.
- Yes, so I mean, I think it's supposed to work like that.
- And the video, boom, perfect.
You hear the sound?
- Yeah, we hear the sound.
(upbeat music)
(singing in foreign language)
- That's crazy.
- Okay, I can zoom, fuck.
But I think, yeah.
(upbeat music)
The quality, the consistency, it's kind of crazy, right?
- Yeah.
(upbeat music)
- Okay, so that's--
- It went crazy on chameleon images.
- Yeah, I like that.
So chat GPT, it's just great music.
- Yeah.
- Chat GPT image with a step change
in details instruction following,
placing, yeah, okay, all of your prompt are fucked.
You need to change everything.
Change your harness, change everything.
- Okay.
- Yeah, that one, okay.
Detailing instruction following,
placing and erasing object accurately
and rendering dense text
with the ability to generate across aspect ratio.
They have way more ratio than nano pro or something,
like it's kind of an interesting feature.
It's also accurate across languages
where you can prompt different, yeah, again,
languages in the same pictures
and able to translate an image or something like that.
So it gets smaller image with less prompting.
Okay, a great precision and control.
Yeah, okay, that's cool.
- That's hard.
- Yeah, yeah.
Like if we're able to generate that,
can conceptualize more sophisticated images
and then actually bring that vision to life effectively.
Able to follow an instruction, element,
choose action, zoom in on the right.
Oh, wait, what?
- Can you zoom in?
Oh, see, that's really good.
- Okay.
- It will be cool if you eventually find out
you used a real image.
- I mean, what do you mean like the real image?
- Yeah, like a real photograph as an example,
because it looks so good.
- I mean, yeah, like you can see like the,
there is no like wrong artifact, right?
Like it looks like a real right grain.
- Yeah, yeah, no longer persons with six or seven fingers.
- Oh, at least not here.
- Yeah.
- I think this example generated
like after 20 hours of rendering.
- But the same is here.
At first you had the issue.
If you just want to print your company name,
inside the image on the logo,
it would always make a typo.
And now it shows you a full letter.
- Yeah, that's not, even like look,
like there is like some different gray that.
- Yeah, like the pen.
- Yeah, and it, yeah, it looks like different pressure
of the world, like of the world.
And there is even like a coffee, coffee mark
on the top corner, that's crazy.
- Like a chapter, blah, blah, blah, yeah, back here.
Boom, boom, strong, stronger across languages
can produce image with non-English text.
That's not only rendered correctly,
but with language that flow currently.
Okay, so that could be one piece.
Like I have an example that that's why it come to mind,
but like you can generate one piece episode with that.
That could be, that's a manga, like that's a, yeah.
If you're a good storyteller, you can generate your manga.
- You can create whatever you want.
- Yeah.
- Well, I'm eager to try something.
- Bro, like that's good.
- So now even manga and comic writers are out of work.
- Yeah, that's good quality.
Who waits in a place like this?
I had no choice.
You came alone, we don't have much time.
Okay, there is, answer the question and get to the point.
Okay, what?
I don't.
(laughing)
- It's an example.
- Yeah, okay.
But yeah, oh shit.
Let's get back to it.
- But it is already live in Jet GPT.
- Yeah, like we're gonna prompt some example after that,
but it's accessible on API and the interface.
Flexible Asper ratio, so yeah, that's like, yeah.
That kind of format, they moded that during the...
- Yeah, you can make different sizes of images.
- I mean that, yeah, like you have to have a use case
for that, like...
- Yeah, but before if you put social media ahead,
it's always hard to get the correct form.
- Yeah, for sure.
But I mean, like for, yeah, I mean for TikTok
or like Instagram posts and stuff, we had that.
So why not?
Visual Throw Partner, Jet GPT image is our first image model
with thinking capabilities, okay, that's it.
When a thinking model is selected in Jet GPT,
image 2.0 can search the web for real-time information,
create multiple distinct images from one prompt,
double-check its own output
and even create functional QR codes, okay.
This allow it to take one more,
on more on the heavy lifting between ID and image,
especially when accuracy, up-to-date information,
consistency, visual cohesion matters.
That would be interesting to see if we can,
yeah, like famous people,
if you can generate some famous people stuff.
Okay, thinking mode searches, okay.
When AI, oh yeah, that's the store,
I think the store they had.
Okay, cool, real world intelligence.
Has an updated knowledge cutoff of December 25, okay.
Enter visual proof or a contradiction of the real number.
And what, okay, there is too much math in here.
I said, good job.
- It works.
- Yeah, it works.
Is it cheaper than mid journey?
Yes, so we have, I have like the pricing here,
pricing, tech, tech, tech,
path, path, path, path.
Tech.
- Yeah, and also the question is,
the consistency is better than mid journey.
If you see the chameleon or the manga,
every frame had the exact same figure in it.
- I think it's because they use the,
like the image reference too, right?
But the consistency is kind of solved, honestly,
even with like Nano Pro, like all of the image,
like all of our thumbnails were like nano-geneted video.
- Banana too.
- Yeah, and I always use the same input
and we have like pretty.
- Yeah, because with mid journey, I don't know,
the last time I used it,
I had issues creating the same image over and over again.
- I mean, yeah, I didn't test mid journey
for the last two years.
Image, so it's basically the same price than 1.5.
T2, input eight, eight for 1.5, 1.5, yeah, okay.
Cash input two, sorry.
So like HDRack, do you compare to those pricing?
Like, do you know the input and output?
Maybe you can look at it, like mid journey pricing.
- Yeah, I don't know if he has a fixed fee for mid journey.
- 'Cause here it are API pricing per million tokens.
So it depends on how many tokens you use per image.
- Yeah, yeah, and like the speed of the generation too,
right, but even here.
- If you prompt like four or 500 images per month,
it can go hard.
- Yeah, no, no, no, 1%.
Nano two.
Nano was at 0.607 for one care resolution
and sent for 2K and 4K 15.
That was quite cheap, but I think the price
is not that crazy.
- Yeah, it's a subscription.
- Yeah, yeah.
Mid journey, mid journey price.
(indistinct)
But you still have like a, okay,
because they use the GPU time.
So it takes like, if generating an image is fast,
then you can have a shit ton of them, right?
Yeah, like HD, I did not choose mid journey since forever.
I'm using like Nano Pro, so a Nano 2 event.
- Yeah, but what are you paying?
Like the basic plan?
(speaks in foreign language)
- Yeah.
'Cause like, yes, three hours of compute,
that's not that much.
- No, and a maximum of 10 jobs queued.
- That's for, that's for video.
Like, do they have the image?
- Yeah, but also depends what you are using it for.
- But unlimited image generation with the last month,
subscribe, boost on our pro omega, and okay.
Tag, unlimited video generation and starts most
we keeps you imagine video private.
(speaks in foreign language)
Unlimited images, okay.
Fuck, okay, that's good.
Is that the same, I have a yearly,
but it's not persistent enough, basic.
- Yeah, so that's like 100 bucks per year.
- Yeah.
I mean, if, yeah, it depends of like how much you make,
right?
Did you use mid journey recently, Mitchell?
- No, I didn't.
I haven't used it a lot
because the overview I had was really bad in Discord.
- Yeah, I think they changed that a long time ago,
like you have the web app, right?
- That's how long I didn't use it.
- Yeah.
Yeah, they have like a studio like that.
- It's the same, like you see in "Tragedy" for Sora.
- Yeah, maybe Sora copy Mitchell.
- Yeah.
- Create, it's (speaks in foreign language)
Okay, whatever.
Where can I, I just want to see images.
- Nope, you need to pay first.
- Okay, so bye.
But also like, it was kind of cheap to,
I mean, I didn't see my subscription on "Cha GPT"
going down because I generated like two images.
So it's, yeah.
I mean, it's kind of included in all stuff.
Anyway, back to the thread,
image was available starting today on "Cha GPT"
and collect user is thinking available to "Cha GPT"
four plus four, okay, so we have that.
Some example below the thread, so that's it, that's it.
Okay, multiple distinct image, yeah, I was thinking, okay.
Okay, okay, no, that's good.
That's high fidelity.
- Yeah, that's good quality.
- Yeah.
But wait, I saw, okay, so I have a couple of images.
Example, yes, tag, tag, path, okay, so this one,
that's all of the base use case for "GPT" images
and the illustration was generated by a "GPT" image too.
So text to image, realistic image, artistic image editing,
because in the conversation in "Cha GPT"
you can edit a video directly in the conversation,
like I think they did that with image one,
so that's an interesting workflow.
Background generation, product visualization,
concept art, character generation, which like, yeah,
if you have like good consistency, that's good.
And you can even like, you know,
have the three by three spreadsheet or characters
and with different angle, so then you validate that
and then you can animate it based on that score.
Pretty tedious.
Background, infographic, UX/UI, storyboarding, okay,
marketing, social media, print, packaging, design,
illustration, photo announcement,
meme and fun creation, and I had another one,
which is tag, one piece, wait, fuck, I didn't save it.
Image nest, blah, blah, blah, fuck, I lost it.
Okay, path, what's really staying?
"Cha GPT" is running out, running out, running out, okay.
Singularity, the new "Cha GPT" image
is a new standard for photorealistic images.
Oh, that's not, that's really good.
- It's a lot of details.
- Yeah. - It is cool.
- Oh, that's nice.
Oh my God.
- I think you have to integrate this one
in your API as well.
- Yeah, we'll be down.
- Well, it should be easy, right?
Everything you developed.
- Yeah, 100%, tag, project, as "Cha GPT".
Oh, wait, share some issues.
- Is front and back.
- Yeah.
- Okay, friends, trying image to grow.
That's nuts.
The hand is a bit weird here, but that's a family picture.
- Yeah, and you just have to look for it
and make some final changes and then it's perfect.
- This is awesome for web shops.
- Yeah, yeah.
I mean, we were already capable to do that with Dano, right?
- Yeah, but each time they make it easier
and even more consistent.
- But that's what, like, bro, like it's,
there is no point of taking pictures anymore.
Like, okay, yeah, you can fake.
- Yeah, the only thing is if you show your daughter
and your wife that you went to Disneyland,
they give them all the pictures,
they won't believe you.
- Yeah, wait, okay.
What's the joke, "Cha GPT"?
What?
Oh, okay, maybe it's the, yeah.
- It's the next one.
- They changed the face too.
That's a lot.
Tag, path, okay.
Okay, why not?
Is that like, fuck, what is his name?
- The white walker.
- No, it's the Jason Momoa.
No?
- No, no, no, he isn't.
- Okay.
- I think.
- Oh, that's a model, okay.
Image two is not online, should have been just a few days.
Even with a three-by-three, would have a struggle.
Now we can do 10x complexity, yeah.
That's kind of cool.
Okay.
mandatory vaccine checkpoint, tax the rich, and.
Okay, so that's really, okay, so like,
pretty nuts.
As you react, like, would you use over like a mid journey
to Cha GPT now, like if you see the images generated
in example?
We'll see if it will play.
- Yes.
- Okay, so that was, this one is like the blog post
on the website.
They have, I don't know if they had it last time,
but like they have the, which is kind of cool.
They have the text version and the image version
of the article.
So they generate like all of those image
with the text they have here.
Like that.
So yeah, interesting Cha GPT image to anywhere
of image generation.
A year ago, we released Cha GPT image during the year,
Jesus, both beautiful and useful.
Image in the next step, set of art,
step change instruction to extend model capability,
the most complete task.
Yeah, whatever, whatever.
Greater precision and control.
But yeah, that's not a screenshot.
- No, no, that was generated.
- Right, it looks perfect.
- Yeah, you can show people your desktop
that you're working.
- Yeah, you can have a background, right?
- Yeah.
Like it's working on my PC.
Yeah, bro, that's a screenshot.
That's crazy.
Create everything at once.
Is that generated?
The rice?
Stronger across languages.
Okay, yes.
Okay, so you can, you can have it like,
okay, you take a translation.
You can take an original of a manga, for example,
and you can do the translation with AI.
And then you can place all of the,
like the dialogue directly into the image and that's it.
- Yeah, you only have to make it once
and then you make it so easier to do the rest.
- Yeah, it's not.
It's Jirak.
I will take a look at it for now.
I'm not, I'm not using MG enough for the price it costs.
Yes.
Why are you based?
Tag, well, okay.
So basically images are solved, bro.
Like no more hard stuff, no more Photoshop,
no more editing, just prompt it.
- Yeah, no, exactly.
And you can edit a picture in the conversation.
I'm gonna show you that right now.
Wow, that's cool.
I even like, yeah, see like the framing
and the disposition of like the design.
It's not like it's all the other, but it's not like
completely like, you know, it stay in the box.
It's like that and it goes above the boxes and stuff.
That's pretty cool.
GPT image and flexible as per ratio.
So we saw that.
That's kind of nice.
Okay, real world intelligence.
Okay, biggest.
Oh yeah, that, okay, so that means the models.
So why it was generating the image?
- Yeah, it also put in the correct math.
- Yeah, so maybe, how can you say if it's real or not?
- Yeah, probably if they show it here, it's correct.
- I hope so for them.
Design trend, yeah, you can do illustrations and stuff.
Wow, that's cool.
I like blue, you can generate that for design,
like website design and stuff.
- Normally a designer would charge you like a lot of money
just to show your product in different angles
and different setups.
Now it's one prompt.
- Yeah, and then we can still charge 15 grand for that.
- Yeah.
- With just one prompt still.
Okay, so that's an ad, let's go.
Copy, okay, syncing, yeah, whatever, whatever.
Okay, cool, let's play a little bit.
- Yes, see what I can do.
- The generation, so, okay.
What I've done for the seminar of this live stream,
live stream, I uploaded on like a little PFP.
- Wow.
- And I took a prompt that I have,
a prompt template that I have from,
Claude, 'cause I have the conversation there,
just before it got cut.
And that's the first one it generated.
And I have three different variations, that one is cool.
All right, I like this one.
- Yeah, and it only had one reference image.
- Yeah, and I didn't upload the OpenAI logo.
- No, no, it just found it.
Well, at least I know it has what the OpenAI logo is.
And it generated that, and after,
yeah, I asked it like to different variation
of the same prompt, because I edited inside the conversation
and like, yeah, it's not, this one is shit, but okay.
So yeah, because I asked to show the different capability
of the model, so different type of illustration,
but then it had like the GPT image and I didn't like that.
But yeah, and this one was another variation.
- But to do it in NANABANANA 2,
we had to put in multiple images of the person, right?
- No, no, no, just one, like one output and stuff, so.
- Okay, that was good.
- That was pretty similar, yeah.
But even to see between the face, like it's the same.
Our face doesn't move, it just like move it,
but keep the consistency between.
- It's like it copy pasted the image.
- 1%, like even here, same position, same everything.
Okay, the hand moved a bit,
but like my face doesn't change yours neither.
Yeah, it's crazy.
Okay, so let's try something else.
Okay, so same thread and yes, okay.
Let's create, imagine a manga page with those two men.
They are meeting in the street, raining, raining.
Midnight, and they are getting ready for a podcast.
Noir at most fair manga style.
Let's see how it goes.
A manga page with those two men,
they are meeting in the street, it's raining, midnight.
Yeah, midnight dark, okay, let's see.
Yeah, now we can also see how fast it is.
- Not that fast.
- Okay.
- So yeah, if you want to talk about something else.
- What did you do today?
No.
- Okay, so.
- Well, the only thing I noticed is that your left menu,
your recent, it's cleared.
I have like 1,000 history videos.
- I have archive everything.
- Oh, okay.
- Okay.
- You clean up before the show.
- Exactly.
- Imagine Elon Musk playing Diablo 3, I'll.
Oh, shit.
- Yeah.
- What is it again?
- I was going to ask,
does it know that when you type imagine
that it needs to generate an image every time?
- Where is it?
- You lost it, it's gone.
- Oh, okay.
Oh.
- Probably you have to refresh the game.
- What?
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
- It is the wrong one, right?
- Yeah, that's a,
that's a, fuck.
It's a Marvel character.
- Yeah, Iron Man.
- And.
- Well, it's Iron Man combined with another one.
- Yeah.
- That's not Elon Musk.
- I want to create and create.
- But.
Okay.
- Now we try to make a game, it looks like.
- Is it?
- In case you had a quest
that gave you what you can do with the side quest,
so it made an idea for a game.
- Ah, okay, interesting.
And for that, ooh, ooh.
Okay, we lost the faces, but.
- Yeah, that doesn't matter.
- Yeah, mine is more like,
yeah, they got, we lost your reference.
But, okay, bro, that's cool.
You made it, yeah, let's do this.
Some conversation don't just happen.
They change everything.
Tonight we build the future, what the fuck?
Make it, not landscape, portrait.
And put these boxes with one big central out.
And keep the same face.
VAF, Elon Musk, W3, okay.
What if, ooh, ooh, holy shit.
It put everything it wrote down around it.
- So yeah, that's a character sheet, so.
- Yeah.
- Elon Musk, techno sorcerer, level 52 CEO, bro, that's sick.
And that's the interface from Diablo 3.
Okay, describe, edit, select.
Yeah, okay, so you can select what you want to edit, okay?
A spare ratio, ultra wide, glory, white portrait.
Landscape square, oh, story, story?
What does it mean, story?
And I want to try, okay,
imagine the last page of one piece.
- Did you need to press the plus and select the image?
Oh, now it does it right away.
- Okay, that was fast as fuck.
The final page, open in silence, no, no, no, no, no.
- I think it just loaded a few images,
it didn't create one because you.
- Oh yeah, it take the resources, oh, bro, that's,
oh, it search for the web and--
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, you didn't press the plus
that you want an image.
- Oh yeah, it's Dr. Strange,
that's the name of the character, like the sorcerer stuff.
- My bad, okay, so perfect.
Now create the image for it.
It is creating the last page of one piece
in live action.
From Netflix, did you have, okay.
Diablo three, boom, okay, so ratio, okay, nice.
Okay, oh, and now, okay, put an alone in the Diablo three
game, the image is a frame of Diablo three.
Three, tough, I character shit,
I think we can animate to create it, nice.
- Ooh, you can make a full comic.
- 100%, boom, boom, okay, so, okay,
which sense do you read it?
Because if it's a manga, it's going right to left, right?
You made it, yeah, let's do this, boom.
Tonight we build the future.
- Storm conversation, don't just tap it, okay, okay.
We need to write to think, to work on the storytelling,
but.
- Yeah, you also need to make a proper prompt,
now it just copies the image.
- Yeah, and this one is the same as like this one.
- Yeah, so you need to tell it in the prompt
that it needs to create a new image for each frame,
but still, it doesn't matter.
- Try asking if it can make this entire page,
but then photo realistic.
I've converted to a photo realistic page.
- Okay, it's photo realistic, realistic, buff.
One piece final scene, ooh.
- See, that's.
- Oh, wait, wait, wait, is that?
Oh, fuck, it's opening the desktop.
It, yeah, I'm gonna do that, but one piece.
Did you watch the TV show?
- Just a few, a few one, not a full show.
That's all, bro, that's the fucking actors.
- And this is not a real scene, right?
This is creative.
- No, no, no, no, that's one of,
like all of the, some characters don't even exist.
Okay, so yeah, Brooke is only on his human form,
like the skeleton, these characters,
okay, you don't see the mouse,
but like this big guy on the right,
he doesn't, he's not happy yet.
And it's not exactly that, but we are like 90% here.
- Yeah, so it actually did a Google search
and it looked up all the characters and put them in here.
Ah, cool, but still you see again
that it takes out the person that we created
and it actually copies it in here.
So the consistency is really good.
(indistinct)
- Okay, so this one.
- Oh, cool, see, it isn't fully, or is it?
- It kind of like colorized it.
- Yeah.
- That's nuts.
Tonight be that big ideas, no filter, real talk, let's go.
That's nuts.
Yeah, that's crazy.
Okay, so what else can we do?
Okay, so path create the image of, imagine.
- Before you press enter, press the plus on the left.
- Paris.
- If you select create image, it works much better.
Yes, imagine Paris in (indistinct)
What can we do to test the capability?
Blueprints, nightmare flash, anime, oh, yeah, wait.
Give me an ad for (indistinct)
That's it.
Let's see if it Googles it.
- Yes, Paris, okay, (indistinct)
Holy fuck.
- Oh, that's cool.
And he even puts a Tesla logo on his back.
- Holy shit, wow.
- You should DM it to Elon.
See if you can get a response.
- Thank you for joining our party on Diablo.
- Shit, shit, no, okay, no, I'm gonna use my account.
I want that, I want that, I will retweet that.
Yeah.
(indistinct)
- No, it can't be triggered, it can't be.
- Welcome to Diablo 3 Templar for glory Elon Musk say,
let's change the world.
- Let's change the world, the one night at a time.
- The world with GGT, no H 2.0, one night.
One night or one night, one night.
- One night, like this, that's better.
Okay, let's change the demo through one at a time, thank you.
Let's see if we can go viral.
Okay, cool.
Paris, shit, I saw the same prompt from London
and it was exactly the same fucking shit.
It still has some stuff that it just reuses every time.
- Yeah, and like it's, yeah, okay,
it's Paris because you have the fucking Eiffel Tower,
but I can tell you there is nothing, yeah.
- The styling is the same.
- Yeah, exactly.
- But then the question is if you give it a better prompt
from, hey, this is cool,
but I expected the aliens to be in it,
so we have a multicultural with aliens and humans,
can you create that, see if it does it differently?
- Because that was the issue I had with Nana Banana One.
It would not just keep on going, creating new stuff,
eventually it would fall back to the main stuff every time.
I'm gonna make the...
The ads for giant feet, okay,
that's a shitty illustration,
but content that connects air that delivers.
Oh, okay.
Janet in second, built every goal.
Yeah, it went on the website.
- Yeah, it does know what you do.
- Yeah.
- Or humans with human touch and smiley face.
You get all happy people.
Give three variation of the end.
Is that gonna output?
That's emotional cost with final page.
Okay, yeah, okay.
I need to, okay.
The empty throne and the next adventure, cool.
Okay.
Create image, illustrate version one.
Cool, Paris, Paris.
- What it did.
- The style is the same, I mean.
- It is the same type of buildings in it,
the same type of trees and plants.
It only added billboards and a few aliens on the street.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's not that crazy, crazy.
You can't really use that.
Okay, add request.
- Now the question is how easy is it?
This looks better.
- That looks like an ad from the 2000s.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You could fly this to all the neighbors in your neighborhood.
- Yeah, you know, with the gradients
and the purple and stuff, yeah, for sure.
- Do you have the idea of generation?
Oh, can we make the view of OpenAI?
I think the view of entropy and property.
Okay, let's see how good it does it with faces.
- I'm curious if it's going to censor it or not.
- Yeah, it should search people on internet, right?
- No, but it should tell me to fuck off
because it's too violent.
- Oh, oh yeah, it depends on how it makes the image.
All right, what, so you have what, okay.
And then the period can disappear and then, okay.
- The end.
- It's weird.
Okay, illustrate, illustrate.
- Yeah, but your prompt is also really short.
- Yeah, that's true.
- Oh, is it always going to make Sam win?
- Yeah, the name, the logo.
- Yeah.
- I'm going to do it there, Chip.
- It only didn't use the cloud logo.
- Oh, okay.
- It even wrote and traffic with a slash in it.
- And true, yeah.
- Like one of them, they took the Wikipedia logo stuff.
- Tech, tech, okay, path.
Open AI.
Come on, copy the image.
Thank you.
Fast, yeah.
Easy, wait.
- I think we should pinch it.
- Yeah, champion.
Champion.
Tech.
Oh, let's go.
- Let's see.
- Okay, something that you have been struggling
to generate with a image model.
- Well, the only thing is company names
or writing a name on a, for example, if you have an office
and you want to write the company name on the door,
it's always giving issues.
- Okay, great.
Page.
Imagine easy read with the focus on the door
with the logo of a ship ship, ship ship deaf on it 90 style.
- Yes.
- Tech.
Ooh, ooh, that's good.
It could have never worked, but it was never the point.
Bro, that's, yeah, you can make a storyboard on that.
- Yeah, yeah, and if you play with it
and just keep improving your prompt,
you can make some really cool stuff.
- Storyboard.
Um, well, storyboard, um, yeah, that's it.
Okay, ship ship deaf, um, uh, window tinting,
auto residential, video tinting.
- It doesn't understand what ship ship is.
- Software development, Unix is user-friendly.
That's good.
- I mean.
- I mean, we have, we have the,
we have the name correct, change the style of the door.
Okay, so what if we have.
- Oh, it's already done.
Oh no.
- What?
- I told to give the message on top that was already done,
but it isn't.
Yeah.
- So, I don't know if it's, it's still being, okay.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Tech, and I wanted to check if they have more.
- Illustration in there.
Ooh, okay.
- That can be hard as well with mirrors.
- GPT 1.5 versus 10 prompt difference is not impressive.
Yeah, yeah, with mirror, yeah,
because you have to have the consistency from one room.
Yeah, uh, that's, that's way cleaner.
- Uh, create an image.
It gave context of the image based on your memory
and your past conversation, create my view.
That's a bit busy, but that's,
that's a movie poster for sure.
Okay.
That's crazy.
Okay, charge it in.
(keyboard clicking)
That's cool.
And generation by this somewhat entity, as yeah, yeah.
Okay.
In free.
- Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
That's, that's a magazine.
All right.
- No more expensive editors needed.
- That's nuts.
Ooh, amazing update will be nano brains cinematography.
Yeah, man.
That's nice with the reflection.
That's pretty cool.
Wow, that's nuts.
- That's crazy.
Okay, that's good.
But okay, so do we have anything?
Okay, it's midnight already.
Do we have anything else we wanted to explore?
- No, I think we already saw a lot.
So I'm pretty curious to see what other people can do.
Yeah.
- That's like, and it's full, like it's copy paste.
Like the characters are copy pasted.
- Nice, nice, nice.
Okay, cool.
That's it.
- Well, it's time to make some images.
- Yes.
Like, yeah, I think it's gonna, it's quite cheap.
I will need to compare the pricing
once it's gonna be on the replicate directly via the API.
But I don't think it's really gonna be expensive.
So.
- So we might have a new main model.
- Yeah, that's gonna, that's gonna, yeah.
That's gonna make something else
in the next few weeks for sure.
We're gonna have some fun.
- Yes, well, looking forward to it.
- Yes, let's go, let's go.
Thank you, Mitchell, for your time.
Thank you, Edgerock, for your participation.
And yeah, if you're here, subscribe, like the video too,
please, thank you, because we need views.
- And follow us.
- And follow us everywhere.
And maybe Elon Musk will do that soon.
So yeah, you could say you were there.
- Yeah, when we created Elon.
- Okay, Mitchell, thank you so much and have a good night.
- Yes, bye.